

CONTACT





+52 (55) 3974 6827



GARO.MONTOYA@GMAIL.COM



PERSONAL

Birthday 5 May 1994

Mexican **Nationality**

Spanish, English Languages

INTERESTS

- REACT DEVELOPMENT
- VISUAL COMUNICATION
- VISUAL EFFECTS
- VIDEO EDITION
- BLOCKCHAIN AND **NEW TECHNOLOGIES**





@GARO MONTOYA



FACEBOOK.COM/GAROMONN

GITHUB.COM/GAROMON

"To have what you have always wanted and never had, requires doing what you have never done "

EDGARDO MONTOYA

COMPUTER SYSTEMS AND DIGITAL ANIMATION ENGR.

PROFILE

Computer Systems And Digital Animation Engr. Computer Systems And Digital Animation Engr. | UNIVERSIDAD Master's in Narrative and Audiovisual Production | PANAMERICANA



Solid knowledge in React library for building user interfaces, Responsive Web Design and the most popular Front End libraries/frameworks in the industry (Bootstrap, Redux, etc...)

Video edition/production and VFX work experience in Great Place to Work-Certified companies and extensive capacity for learning and teaching.

INTERMEDIATE ADVANCED HTML **JQUERY** ADVANCED **EXPERIENCED** CSS REACT **JAVASCRIPT** INTERMEDIATE INTERMEDIATE REDUX **ADOBE CC** SASS INTERMEDIATE **EXPERT BOOTSTRAP**

WORK EXPERIENCE



ASSISTANT MANAGER - CANADA FREELANCE 2020 CANADA

Freelance and Learning Experience in Vancouver with VFS teacher.



AUDIOVISUAL DESIGNER - DANONE/BONAFONT 2018-2020 ●

ADVANCED

BEC, CDMX

Audiovisual Designer | Content creation, video edition and graphic material Management of Creative Area



FORD CREDIT 2017-2018

FORD CREDIT SANTA FE, CDMX

Learning & Development Analyst | Internal and regional communication.



APPLE 2016-2017 ●

APPLE VIA SANTA FE, CDMX

Operation Specialist at Mexico's first Apple Store, managing inventories and logistics issues, in addition to providing customer service | SAP Software



2015 BUSINESKIDS

SAN ANGEL, CDMX

WebMaster Internship | Administration of Company Web Pages



2013 • **IMAGINATION FILMS**

CDMX

3D Artist Internship | Creation of rigg bones of company 3D characters.



EDUCATION

COMPUTER SYSTEMS AND DIGITAL ANIMATION ENGR.

UNIVERSIDAD PANAMERICANA Combines equal parts of computer science and digital art that allows me to use new technologies to develop:

- Mobile applications
- Special effects
- 2D and 3D Animation
- Digital Illustration
- Web Platforms

MASTER'S IN NARRATIVE AND AUDIOVISUAL PRODUCTION

UNIVERSIDAD PANAMERICANA Used as a certification method of the Engr.

- Audiovisual Production process.
- Content Development
- 'Narrative analysis
- VFX
- Photography

CERTIFICATIONS

Responsive Web Design | CodeCamp.org JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures | CodeCamp.org Front End Development Libraries | CodeCamp.org

